Guide to the Steve Waldron Papers 1976-1985
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
Steve Waldron Papers
1976-1985
University of Montana, Mansfield Library, Archives and Special Collections The University of Montana--Missoula Missoula, MT 59812 406-243-2053 http://www.lib.umt.edu/asc library.archives@umontana.edu
Mss 186
Waldron, Steve, 1946-
12 linear feet 24 boxes
Steve Waldron was a member of the Montana House of Representatives from 1977 to 1985, representing Missoula. He focused on issues related to women, workers, and education.
Biographical Note
Steve Waldron was born September 19, 1946, in Crosby, Minnesota. He moved to Butte, Montana, in 1949 and attended Butte schools. In 1967, he moved to Missoula, Montana, where he was a sawmill worker.
Waldron served in the Montana House of Representatives from 1977 to 1985, representing Missoula Districts 97 and 58 as a Democrat. He focused on issues related to women, workers, and education.
This collection includes organizational papers, correspondence files, research materials, reference reports, and newspaper clippings generated and collected by Steve Waldron during his tenure in the Montana House of Representatives. Correspondence in this collection represents both incoming and outgoing materials ranging across a spectrum of legislative topics and includes constituents, elected officials, state employees, legislative staff members, and professional researchers. The research files in this collection often contain marked-up or final copies of state legislation, handwritten notes, and testimonial transcriptions. Materials in this collection present insights into the internal workings of the Montana State Legislature in the years following adoption of the 1972 Montana Constitution, Waldron's representative and legislative approach, and prominent issues of concern during the time period.
The collection is divided into five series:
Series I: Appointment Book, 1 folder, 1981
Series II: Correspondence, 3.5 linear feet, 1976-1985
Series III: Research Files, 7.0 linear feet, 1932-1985
Series IV: Reports, 0.5 linear feet, undated
Series V: Clippings, 90.5 linear feet, 1977-1983
Researchers must use collection in accordance with the policies of Archives and Special Collections, the Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, and The University of Montana--Missoula.
The materials were in Waldron's possession until time of donation to the Archives.
Gift of Steve Waldron, 1985 and 1989.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Montana. Legislature. House of Representatives; Democratic Party (Mont.)
Montana--Politics and government--20th century
Education and state--Montana; Labor laws and legislation -- Montana; Women--Legal status, laws, etc.--Montana
Legislation--Montana
Montana; Women
Legislators--Montana
- Appointment Book, 1981; Series I; 1 folder
  This series consists of one daily appointment book kept by Steve Waldron during the 1981 Montana Legislative Session.
  - 1981 (Box-folder 1/1)
- Correspondence, 1976-1985; Series II; 3.5 linear feet
  This series contains incoming and outgoing correspondence ranging across a spectrum of legislative topics. Correspondents include constituents, elected officials, state employees, legislative staff members, and professional researchers. Topics include action requests, legislative strategies, and inquiries on behalf of constituents. These materials provide insights into the internal workings of the Montana Legislature in the years following passage of the current State Constitution and Steve Waldron's approach to his legislative responsibilities.
  - Outgoing, Legislature, 1977 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Legislative Session, March 1977 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Legislative Session, February 1977 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Gambling, 1977 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Displaced Homemakers, 1977 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Outgoing, 1977 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Outgoing, 1978 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Outgoing, 1979 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Incoming, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Outgoing, Legislature, 1979 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Incoming, Legislature, 1979 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Chairmanship, Outgoing, January 1979 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Appropriations Committee, Incoming, 1979 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Incoming, 1981 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Outgoing, 1983 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Legislative Session, January 1985 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Legislative Session, February 1985 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Legislative Session, February 1985 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Legislative Session, February 1985 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Legislative Session, February 1985 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Legislative Session, February 1985 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Legislative Session, February - March 1985 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Legislative Session, February - March 1985 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Legislative Session, March 1985 (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Legislative Session, March 1985 (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Incoming, March - April 1985 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Legislative Session, April 1985 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - General, 1976 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - General, January 1977 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - General, January 1977 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - General, January 1977 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - General, February 1977 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - General, February 1977 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - General, March - May 1977 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - General, June - November 1977 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - General, 1978 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - General, January 1979 (Box-folder 5/5)
  - General, February 1979 (Box-folder 5/6)
  - General, March 1979 (Box-folder 5/7)
  - General, May - December 1979 (Box-folder 5/8)
  - General, 1980 (Box-folder 5/9)
  - General, January 1981 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - General, February 1981 (Box-folder 5/11)
  - General, March 1981 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - General, April 1981 (Box-folder 6/2)
  - General, 1982 (Box-folder 6/3)
  - General, January 1983 (Box-folder 6/4)
  - General, February 1983 (Box-folder 6/5)
  - General, February 1983 (Box-folder 6/6)
  - General, March 1983 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - General, March 1983 (Box-folder 6/8)
  - General, January - May 1985 (Box-folder 6/9)
  - General, undated (Box-folder 7/1)
  - General, undated (Box-folder 7/2)
  - General, undated (Box-folder 7/3)
  - General, undated (Box-folder 7/4)
- Research Files, 1932-1985; Series III; 7.0 linear feet
  This series contains research files collected by Steve Waldron during his tenure in the Montana State Legislature and are organized by subject (following his original headings). Files in this series contain a mix of legislative bills (both marked-up and final copies), Waldron's handwritten notes, transcriptions of testimony, and legislative staff reports. Most materials relate directly to bills before the Legislature (often bills that received attention across several sessions); however, some files concern topics of interest to Steve Waldron that never reached the level of formal legislative introduction. These materials provide insights into the internal workings of the Montana Legislature and Steve Waldron's focal issues.
  - ATV Laws, undated (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Aging Services, undated (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Aging Study, SJR 28, undated (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Agister's Lien, HB 204, undated (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Agrischool, HB 815, undated (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Aircraft Pool, undated (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Alcohol, HB 420, undated (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Division, undated (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Alcoholism, undated (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Alcohol Tax, HB 439, undated (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Alcohol Tax, HB 651, undated (Box-folder 8/11)
  - All-terrain Vehicles, HB 633, undated (Box-folder 8/12)
  - Ambulance Districts, HB 240, undated (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Alternative Fuel Tax, HB 17, LP 6, undated (Box-folder 8/14)
  - Amending County Budget Laws, HB 477, undated (Box-folder 8/15)
  - Amendments, HB 447, undated (Box-folder 8/16)
  - Annual Intake Unit Activities, 1983 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Annual Visits to Nursing Homes, HB 165, undated (Box-folder 8/18)
  - Anti-child Zoning, undated (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Appropriations Bills, undated (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Appropriations Bills, 1977 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Appropriating Funds, HB 416, undated (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Appropriation Committee, Memberships and Meeting Room, undated (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Arts Council, January 1985 (Box-folder 8/24)
  - Assistance Payments, undated (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Attorney General, Consumer Affairs, HB 590, undated (Box-folder 8/26)
  - Audit Bureau, January 1981 (Box-folder 8/27)
  - Audit and Program Compliance, undated (Box-folder 8/28)
  - Audit Committee Bills, undated (Box-folder 8/29)
  - Boulder River School and Hospital, undated (Box-folder 8/30)
  - Bad Checks, HB 751, undated (Box-folder 8/31)
  - Bank Share Tax Subcommittee, HB 735-1817, undated (Box-folder 8/32)
  - Battered Spouses, HB 800, undated (Box-folder 8/33)
  - Battered Wives, HB 780, undated (Box-folder 8/34)
  - Beer and Wine, HB 374, undated (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Bills that May Decrease Revenue of Local Courts, undated (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Board of Pardons, undated (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Board of Real Estate, HB 846, undated (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Bonding Mortgage, Finance and Insurance, HB 714, undated (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Bonding Removal, SB 125, undated (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Boulder, undated (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Budget Bill, SB 235, undated (Box-folder 9/8)
  - CMHC, undated (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Canyon Ferry, undated (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Center for the Aged, undated (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Central Office, undated (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Central Office and Management Services, undated (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Centralized Funding for School Foundation, HB 809, undated (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Certificate of Need, HB 458, undated (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Child Abuse, HJR 69, undated (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Child/Maternal Health/Dental, undated (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Children Trust Fund, SB 19, HB 252, HB 540, undated (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Cigarette Fair Sales Act Repeal, HB 106, undated (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Cigarette Sales, HB 681, undated (Box-folder 9/20)
  - Cigarette Sales, Exempt, HB 518, undated (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Cigarette Tax, HB 45, undated (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Civil Attorney (County), HB 133, undated (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Clarice Cushman, undated (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Classification Limits, HB 806, undated (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Coal Tax, SB 44, undated (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Coal Tax Trust Fund, undated (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Coal Tax Funding for Parks, HB 77, undated (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Coal Tax Giveaway, HB 607, undated (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Community-Based Corrections, undated (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Conduct of Business and Local Government, HB 859, undated (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Consolidated Services, HB 760, undated (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Co-payment, HB 731, undated (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Corrections, undated (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Corrections Division, undated (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Counseling Cost for Rape and Incest, HB 44, undated (Box-folder 10/12)
  - County Budget Law, HB 477, undated (Box-folder 10/13)
  - County Impact, undated (Box-folder 10/14)
  - County Salaries, SB 50, undated (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Crime, undated (Box-folder 10/16)
  - DCA Reorganization, undated (Box-folder 10/17)
  - DDD, undated (Box-folder 10/18)
  - DHES Requirements, HB 206, undated (Box-folder 10/19)
  - DOL Supplement, undated (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Day Care, SA-HB 646, undated (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Definition of Non-Highway Vehicles, HB 871, undated (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Department of Health and Environmental Sciences, undated (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Department of Health and Environmental Sciences, undated (Box-folder 10/24)
  - Department of Highways, undated (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Department of Institutions, HB 450, undated (Box-folder 10/26)
  - Department of Labor, undated (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Displaced Homemakers, HB 400, undated (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Displaced Homemakers, undated (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Displaced Homemakers, HB 623, undated (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Drug and Alcohol Dependence, HB 419, undated (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Eastmont, undated (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Eastmont, undated (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Education, undated (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Elected Officials, undated (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Election, 1978 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Eligibility Tax, SRS, undated (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Ethics File, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Family Violence, SB 449, undated (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Federal Highway Proposals and Construction, undated (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Fees for Heavy Drugs, HB 6, undated (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Fire Marshal, HB 132, HB 162, undated (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Fiscal Analysis, undated (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Fiscal Change, SB 412, undated (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Fish and Game Commission, HB 791, undated (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Food and Consumer Safety, Air Quality, Solid Waste Management, and Occupational Health, undated (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Form Letter, undated (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Four Cs and Day Care, undated (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Foster Care and Group Home, undated (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Friends to Youth, undated (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Friends to Youth, Mental Health, 1985 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Gambling in America, undated (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Game Bird Licensing, HB 568, undated (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Garbage District Elections, Apelstad, SB 343, undated (Box-folder 12/13)
  - General Assistance for Single Parents, 1985 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Genetics, Shodair Hospital, HB 430, undated (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Government Bonds Revision, SB 307, undated (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Grace Periods for Motor Registration, HB 125, undated (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Grandparent Visitation Rights, HB 88, undated (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Grizzly Bear Habitat, HJR 68, undated (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Gross Procedes, HB 198, undated (Box-folder 12/20)
  - HB 421, undated (Box-folder 12/21)
  - HB 500, undated (Box-folder 12/22)
  - HB 538, undated (Box-folder 12/23)
  - HB 714, undated (Box-folder 12/24)
  - HURA, undated (Box-folder 12/25)
  - Health Department Pass Through, HB 289, undated (Box-folder 12/26)
  - Higher Education Revision, HB 80, undated (Box-folder 12/27)
  - Highway Department, undated (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Highway Department, undated (Box-folder 12/29)
  - Highway Sufficiency, HB 9, undated (Box-folder 12/30)
  - Highways, HJR 56, undated (Box-folder 12/31)
  - Historical Society, 1985 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Homestead Exemption, HB 668, undated (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Homestead Tax Relief, HB 828, undated (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Hotel Tax, HB 393, HB 392, undated (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Hotel Tax, HB 427, undated (Box-folder 13/5)
  - House Appropriations Committee Report, HB 500, undated (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Housing, Student, undated (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Human Resources, undated (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Human Rights Commission, undated (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Incentive Programs, HB 73, HB 875, undated (Box-folder 13/10)
  - Income Tax Privacy, HB 157, undated (Box-folder 13/11)
  - Indian Education, HB 707, HJR 56, undated (Box-folder 13/12)
  - Institution Cost and Policy, undated (Box-folder 13/13)
  - Institutions, Final Actions, undated (Box-folder 13/14)
  - Institutions, undated (Box-folder 13/15)
  - Joint Custody, HB 717, undated (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Joint Custody, SB 152, undated (Box-folder 13/17)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Appropriations, undated (Box-folder 13/18)
  - Junk Food, HB 115, undated (Box-folder 13/19)
  - LRB Veterans Home, undated (Box-folder 13/20)
  - Lactrile, HB 97, undated (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Land Use, HB 630, undated (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Law Enforcement Amendments, HB 122, undated (Box-folder 14/3)
  - LC Center for the Aged, undated (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Lecture to NCSL, undated (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Legal Indexes, 1981 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Legislation, undated (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Legislation, 1979 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Legislative Auditor, undated (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Legislative Auditor, undated (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Legislative Bills, Status Sheets, and Committees, 1979 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Legislative Materials, undated (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Levy, HB 191, undated (Box-folder 14/13)
  - Liability Insurance, HB 157, undated (Box-folder 15/1)
  - Library Supplemental (Crabtree v. Library), December 1984 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Liquor, HB 447, undated (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Liquor Tax, HB 627, undated (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Liquor Sales, HB 564, undated (Box-folder 15/5)
  - Lobbyists, undated (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Lobbyist Disclosure, undated (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Local Government, undated (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Local Government Code, SJR 319, undated (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Local Government Revision, HB 851, undated (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Local Montana Revenue, HJR 61, undated (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Long Range Planning, January 1985 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Montana Conservation Corps, HB 823, undated (Box-folder 15/13)
  - MYTC, undated (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Mandatory Retirement Report, undated (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Marriage License Fee, HB 45, undated (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Medicaid, February 1985 (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Medical Assistance, undated (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Medical Assistance, Medicaid, undated (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Meeting with Governor, undated (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Mental Health, HB 202, undated (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Mental Health and Residential Services, undated (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Midwifery, HB 587, undated (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Midwifery, HB 514, undated (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Mining Restrictions, SB 278, undated (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Legislation, undated (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Montana Forest and Conservation, Experimental Station, Biennial Reports, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Montana Perinatal Program, January - March 1985 (Box-folder 16/14)
  - Montana State Hospital, February 1985 (Box-folder 16/15)
  - Montana Youth Center, HB 878, undated (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Motor Fee Increase, HB 870, undated (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Motor Rules and Regulations, undated (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Motor Vehicle Fee, Court and Lock Grant, HB 870, undated (Box-folder 16/19)
  - Motor Vehicle Tax, undated (Box-folder 16/20)
  - Mountain View, January 1985 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - Mountain View Juvenile Justice, HB 667, undated (Box-folder 16/22)
  - Municipal Courts, HB 217, undated (Box-folder 16/23)
  - Municipal Courts, SB 217, undated (Box-folder 16/24)
  - Natural Resources and Business Regulation, undated (Box-folder 16/25)
  - Naturopathic Medicine, HB 435, undated (Box-folder 16/26)
  - Office of Public Instruction, January 1985 (Box-folder 16/27)
  - Payments in Lieu of Tax, HB 516, undated (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Pay Plan, undated (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Personal Privilege, Paul Prestoria, undated (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Physicians Assistant, Keyser, undated (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Pine Hills, undated (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Pine Hills, undated (Box-folder 17/6)
  - Planning Issues, Disease, Facilities, Legal Issues, undated (Box-folder 17/7)
  - Pregnant Teens, HJR 19, undated (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Press Releases, 1975 (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Priorities for People, undated (Box-folder 17/10)
  - Priorities for People, undated (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Prison, undated (Box-folder 17/12)
  - Prison, undated (Box-folder 17/13)
  - Prison Charges, undated (Box-folder 17/14)
  - Prison Industries, HB 490, undated (Box-folder 17/15)
  - Prison Care, undated (Box-folder 17/16)
  - Prison Ranch, undated (Box-folder 17/17)
  - Prison Reimbursement, undated (Box-folder 17/18)
  - Prison Relief Value, HB 546, undated (Box-folder 17/19)
  - Pro-Choice, undated (Box-folder 17/20)
  - "Profile of a Lawmaker," by Bruce E. Nelson, undated (Box-folder 17/21)
  - Program Planning, ADAP, undated (Box-folder 17/22)
  - Property Management, undated (Box-folder 17/23)
  - Property Tax, undated (Box-folder 17/24)
  - Property Tax, HB 3, undated (Box-folder 17/25)
  - Public Works Contracted, HB 695, undated (Box-folder 17/26)
  - Reapportionment by Legislature, SB 238, undated (Box-folder 17/27)
  - Regulation of Water Well Contractors, HB 806, undated (Box-folder 17/28)
  - Renal Program, undated (Box-folder 17/29)
  - Reuse and Recycling Act, HB 2, undated (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Revenue and Spending Projects, undated (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Revenue Resolution, HJR 9, undated (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Retirement Contingency, HB 842, undated (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Revenue Estimates, undated (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Revenue Sharing, Vincent Bill, undated (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Revenue vs. Spending Forecast, undated (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Revision of Public Funding, HB 289, undated (Box-folder 18/8)
  - SB 4, undated (Box-folder 18/9)
  - SID Consolidation, SB 345, undated (Box-folder 18/10)
  - SID Deferral, undated (Box-folder 18/11)
  - SID Deferral, undated (Box-folder 18/12)
  - SJR 29 Status Offenders, undated (Box-folder 18/13)
  - SRS, undated (Box-folder 18/14)
  - SRS Assistance Payments, undated (Box-folder 18/15)
  - SRS Vocational Rehabilitation, undated (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Safety Equipment, HB 777, undated (Box-folder 18/17)
  - Salary Bill, undated (Box-folder 18/18)
  - School for the Deaf and Blind, undated (Box-folder 18/19)
  - School Foundation, Centralization, HB 538, undated (Box-folder 18/20)
  - School Funding, undated (Box-folder 18/21)
  - Select Committee on Aging, undated (Box-folder 18/22)
  - Senior Citizens, HB 679, undated (Box-folder 18/23)
  - Service Distribution, HB 115, undated (Box-folder 18/24)
  - Service Fees, SB 207, undated (Box-folder 18/25)
  - Services to Disabled Persons, HB 909, SJR 9, undated (Box-folder 18/26)
  - Shortfalls in Revenue, HB 715, undated (Box-folder 18/27)
  - Snowmobile, HB 158, undated (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Social Services, undated (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Social Services Rehabilitation, undated (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Social Services Rehabilitation, undated (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Special Olympics, HB 410, undated (Box-folder 19/5)
  - State Assembly District Courts, undated (Box-folder 19/6)
  - State Banks, HB 786, undated (Box-folder 19/7)
  - State Budget Committee Papers, undated (Box-folder 19/8)
  - State Equalization of School Funding, HB 809, undated (Box-folder 19/9)
  - State Government Food Purchases, undated (Box-folder 19/10)
  - State Library, undated (Box-folder 19/11)
  - State Mandates, HB 61, undated (Box-folder 19/12)
  - State School Mandate, HB 207, undated (Box-folder 19/13)
  - Status Sheets, undated (Box-folder 19/14)
  - Subcommittee Newsletter, 1985 (Box-folder 19/15)
  - Subdivision Fee, HB 179, undated (Box-folder 19/16)
  - Submission of Balanced Budget, SJR 15, undated (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Sunset Audit, undated (Box-folder 19/18)
  - Sunset Law, undated (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Swan River Forest Camp, undated (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Taxation, undated (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Taxation, undated (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Taxation, undated (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Temporary TRO, undated (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Third Reading Bills, undated (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Tourist Tax, HB 280, HB 599, HB 230, undated (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Transfer of Custody to SRS, HB 489, undated (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Unemployed Parent, SB 122, undated (Box-folder 21/4)
  - University Funding, LFA, undated (Box-folder 21/5)
  - University Special Session, Funding, Medicaid, Vo-tech, undated (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Urban Transportation District, undated (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Vehicle Fee, HB 483, undated (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Veteran Affairs, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Veterans Home, undated (Box-folder 21/10)
  - Veterans Home, undated (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Video Testimony from Incest Victims, HB 61, undated (Box-folder 21/12)
  - Vision Quest, HB 684, undated (Box-folder 21/13)
  - Visual Services, undated (Box-folder 21/14)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation, undated (Box-folder 21/15)
  - Vo-tech, undated (Box-folder 21/16)